https://www.pilotguides.com/legal/

View the series
Search DISCLAIMER: This is the website of Pilot Film & Television Productions Ltd.Pilot Productions aims to provide comprehensive and accurate information on a range of travel locations depicted via our TV shows, our websites – www.pilotguides.com – (“the Websites”), and merchandise (DVDs, videos, music CDs, books, maps, etc.)We cannot, however, account for information which may be out of date or inaccurate due to changes in conditions, economic or political circumstances. If you plan to follow a trip suggested by us or visit a country, town or region, we recommend you contact the nearest national tourist board for up-to-date information, particularly regarding currency exchange rates and safety.Pilot Productions cannot accept any responsibility for damages, loss, accident or injury incured when following one of our suggested guides or activities.PRIVACY POLICY: Pilot Film & TV Productions Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy as a user of our Websites – and the confidentiality of any personal information that you may provide us with during your visit to our Websites.Pilot is fully compliant with the terms and conditions of the UK Data Protection Act of 1998 and is committed to protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of any personal information that you may provide during the course of your visit to our Websites.Information is gathered automatically by our web server, through the use of cookies* on the websites, and also through the submissions of online forms. General information collected by the web server – not requiring end-user input is the following:1. browser (type and version) 2. operating system 3. IP address 4. domain name 5. geographic location 6. connection speedThe information we collect is used for internal review only and is used to optimise the content and quality of our Websites.Our commitment to your privacy:Your privacy is important to us and the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us should you have any concerns.This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.pilotguides.com or our associated websites (the “Sites”).Pilot Productions and its distributor in North America, 555 Productions Inc, is fully compliant with the terms and conditions of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of 2016 protecting  your privacy  and the confidentiality of any personal information that you may provide during the course of your visit to our websites (“Sites”).Personal information we collect:When you visit our Sites, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Sites, and information about how you interact with the Sites. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:1. “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.2. “Log files” track actions occurring on the Sites, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.3. “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Sites, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.How do we use your personal information:We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:1. Communicate with you;2. Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and3. When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).  Device information may be used for Advertising or Retargeting our products that may be relevant to you (see Behavioral Advertising below.)Sharing your personal information:We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Big Commerce to power our online store–you can read more about how Big Commerce  uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Behavioral advertising:As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting the following sites:FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.Do not track:Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.Your rights:If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.Data retention:When you place an order through the Sites, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.Changes:We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.Online Forms:By subscribing to the Pilot Guides e-newsletter, any information that you provide online is captured into our database. This information is used to keep you updated with news and promotions about our TV shows and merchandise. We do not share, rent, or sell our subscriber lists to any other company, organisation, or third party.*Cookies: A cookie is a text-only string that is entered into the memory of your browser by our web server. The use of cookies enables our Websites to store information on your PC so that it can be retrieved at a later date. This is done so that we can monitor the number of people visiting our Websites and to determine the country of origin of specific users. If you do not wish to accept new cookies or wish to disable cookies altogether, you can set your browser accordingly using its menu bar.COPYRIGHT:Unless otherwise stated, the copyright and any other rights in all material on our Websites are the property of Pilot Film & TV Productions Ltd. You are permitted to print and download extracts from this site on the following conditions:1. Use of documents and related graphics on the Websites is for information and/or personal, non-commercial use only;2. Any copies of pages saved from the Websites onto disk – or to any other storage medium – may only be used for subsequent viewing purposes or to print extracts for personal, non-commercial use only;3. No documents or related graphics on the Websites are to be modified in any way;4. Graphics on the Websites are not to be used separately from the accompanying text and Pilot Productions copyright notice – © Pilot Productions 2008 – must appear on all copies;5. No part of this site may be reproduced or stored in any other website without Pilot Productions’ prior written consent.PILOT FILM & TELEVISION PRODUCTIONS LTD Registered company Number: 02643675 The Old Studio, 18 Middle Row, London W10 5AT, United Kingdom  View our Product CataloguePilot Guides Store DTO Bundle: Ultimate Blitzkrieg: The WW2 Battle of CreteThis three part documentary tells the... SHOP DVD: Ultimate Blitzkrieg: The WW2 Battle of CreteThis three part documentary tells the... SHOP DTO: Convict AustraliaA Short History of Convict Australia is... SHOP DVD: Empire Builders - British EmpireFORMAT: REGION-FREE DVD - Plays... SHOPBe the first to know…Be the first to know...Sign up for our free monthly eNews now, and receive exclusive updates on new releases, giveaways and VIP offers Sign up
News
A spotlight on Nicaragua The largest country in Central...
Remembrance, Veterans and Armistice Day... November 11, 2020 Remembrance Day,...
It's all eyes on America It's been all eyes on the US this week...
Ethiopia: Destination of the Month Quite simply, Ethiopia is one of... Tweets Tweets by @pilotguidestv
